Finding aid to the Classes of 1901-1910 records CA.MS.01020
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1901-1910 records
1897-1984
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1901.
CA.MS.01020
138.625 linear feet (242 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1901-1910 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College. Class of 1901.; Smith College. Class of 1902.; Smith College. Class of 1903.; Smith College. Class of 1904.; Smith College. Class of 1905.; Smith College. Class of 1906.; Smith College. Class of 1907.; Smith College. Class of 1908.; Smith College. Class of 1909.; Smith College. Class of 1910.; Smith College -- Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College -- Students.; Smith College. Class of 1902.; Smith College. Class of 1903.; Smith College. Class of 1904.; Smith College. Class of 1905.; Smith College. Class of 1906.; Smith College. Class of 1907.; Smith College. Class of 1908.; Smith College. Class of 1909.; Smith College. Class of 1910.; Smith College -- Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College -- Students.
- Class of 1901 Records, 1897-1982; 12.5 linear feet (27 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1901 was the twenty-third entering and graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1901 records, 1897-1982, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1901, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, financial information, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - General, undated (Box 1592, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1901 (Box 1592, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1901 (Box 1592, Folder 3)
  - Commencement- Photographs, 1901 (Box 1592, Folder 4)
  - Commencement- Music, 1901 (Box 1592, Folder 5)
  - Financial (gifts, bequests, etc.), 1962-1975 (Box 1592, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind by 1900, 1897 (Box 1592, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1897-1898 (Box 1592, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1897-1901 (Box 1592, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1901 (Box 1592, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day- Photographs, 1901 (Box 1592, Folder 11)
  - Junior Frolic, 1900 (Box 1592, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom, 1900 (Box 1592, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom Picnic, 1900 (Box 1592, Folder 14)
  - Junior-Senior Party for Class of 1900 (Box 1592, Folder 15)
  - Ledger, 1916-1971 (Box 1593, Folder 1)
  - Letters, 1951-1971 (Box 1593, Folder 2)
  - May Lewis- Ellen Emerson Memorial Fund- correspondence, 1960-1976 (Box 1593, Folder 3)
  - May Lewis- Ellen Emerson Memorial Fund- history, financial, 1921-1970 (Box 1593, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1897-1976 (Box 1593, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 1916-1971 (Box 1593, Folder 6)
  - Officers, 1955-1977 (Box 1593, Folder 7)
  - Reunion Notices from Alumnae Quarterly, 1913-1967 (Box 1593.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1902 (Box 1593.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1906 (Box 1593.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1911 (Box 1593.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1913 (Box 1593.1, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1916 (Box 1593.1, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1921 (Box 1593.1, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1926 (Box 1593.1, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1931-1936 (Box 1593.1, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 1593.1, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1946 (Box 1593.1, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1950-1951 (Box 1593.1, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 1593.1, Folder 13)
  - Reunions Letters, 1961 (Box 1593.1, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 1593.1, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 1593.1, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 1593.1, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 1593.1, Folder 18)
  - Round Robin, 1982 (Box 1593.1, Folder 19)
  - Class Secretary, 1946-1970 (Box 1594, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Notebook, 1901-1971 (Box 1594, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1901 (Box 1594, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1901 (Box 1594, Folder 4)
  - Senior Party at Morris House, 1901 (Box 1594, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1897 (Box 1594, Folder 6)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1594, Folder 7)
  - Class Suppers, 1901 (Box 1594, Folder 8)
  - Class Supper, 1902 (Box 1594, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1901- Alumnae Quarterly Notices
    - Ainslie-Burns, 1912-1970 (Box 1595, Folder 1)
    - Caldwell-Durkee, 1912-1973 (Box 1595, Folder 2)
    - Fales-Grumbine, 1912-1970 (Box 1595, Folder 3)
    - Hanna-Lord, 1909-1970 (Box 1595, Folder 4)
    - Mason-Putman, 1910-1971 (Box 1595, Folder 5)
    - Reeves-Sutton, 1910-1970 (Box 1595, Folder 6)
    - Taylor-Zink, 1910-1971 (Box 1595, Folder 7)
  - Individuals A-B (Box 1596)
  - Individuals C (Box 1596.1)
  - Individuals Da-De (Box 1597)
  - Individuals Di-Ga (Box 1598)
  - Individuals Gi-L (Box 1599)
  - Individuals M (Box 1600)
  - Individuals N-Sh (Box 1601)
  - Individuals Sl-Sm (Box 1602)
  - Individuals Sp-Z (Box 1603)
  - Aull, Mary Wilson (photo album) (Box 1603.1)
  - Batchelder, Alice L. (photo album) (Box 1604)
  - Benson, Mary Eva (photo album) (Box 1603.1)
  - Carle, Katherine Elizabeth (photo album) (Box 1605)
  - Clifford, Dora Louise (memorabilia book and photo albums) (Box 1606)
  - Coakley, Elizabeth Tew (photo album) (Box 1607)
  - Croll, Elsie Lydia (photo albums) (Box 1606.1)
  - Cummings, Alice (scrapbook) (Box 1606.2)
  - Davidson, E. Schureaman (photo album) (Box 1610.1)
  - Dewey, Mildred Winslow (photo album) (Box 1607)
  - Duckworth, Alice France (photo album) (Box 1604)
  - Ganes, Ruth (Ladies of Grecourt) (Box 1609.1)
  - Hood, Susan Mabel (correspondence, memorabilia) (Box 1610)
  - Mead, Mabel Converse (photo album) (Box 1610.1)
  - Pooke, Florence Augusta (memorabilia book) (Box 1610.2)
  - Reeves, Florence (memorabilia book) (Box 1611)
  - Saunders, Caroline Rhodes (photo album) (Box 1611.1)
  - Thome, Anna Valentine (photo album) (Box 1603.1)
  - Valentine, Frances (photo album) (Box 1611.1)
- Class of 1902 Records, 1898-1972; 11.0 linear feet (21 containers)
  The Class of 1902 was the twenty-fourth entering class and the twenty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1902 records, 1898-1967, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1902, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, financial information, and other memorabilia. The Class of 1902 records also includes a necrology from the Class Secretary's notes.
  - Class animal, undated (Box 1613, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photos, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1898 (Box 1613, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Grind, 1898 (Box 1613, Folder 8)
  - Fund Letters, 1905-1964 (Box 1613, Folder 9)
  - Groups, 1898-1902 (Box 1613, Folder 10)
  - Groups, 1898-1902 (Box 1613, Folder 11)
  - History, undated (Box 1613, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day Photos, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 14)
  - Junior-Senior Dance, 1902 (Box 1613, Folder 15)
  - Junior Frolic, 1901 (Box 1613, Folder 16)
  - Junior Prom, 1901 (Box 1613, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1910-1962 (Box 1613, Folder 18)
  - Memorial Gifts, 1919-1929 (Box 1613, Folder 19)
  - Organization, undated (Box 1613, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1903-1910 (Box 1614, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1910-1920 (Box 1614, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1920-1930 (Box 1614, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1931-1935 (Box 1614, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 1614, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 1614, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 1614, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1950-1955 (Box 1614, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 1614, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1962; 1967 (Box 1614, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 1614, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1614, Folder 12)
  - Reunion Scrapbook (Box 1614.1)
  - Senior Dramatics, script, 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photos, 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships, undated (Box 1615, Folder 6)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1898-1899 (Box 1615, Folder 7)
  - Songs, General, undated (Box 1615, Folder 8)
  - Class Supper, 1902 (Box 1615, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1902- Class Secretary's Records: Necrology
    - Class Secretary's Notes: Necrology (Box 1616, Folder 1)
    - Barnes, Blanche Elizabeth (Box 1616, Folder 2)
    - Brown, Edith Werner (Box 1616, Folder 3)
    - Crandall, Leona (Box 1616, Folder 4)
    - Demond, Anna Louise (Box 1616, Folder 5)
    - Dowling, Florence Louise (Box 1616, Folder 6)
    - Drake, Harriet Frances (Box 1616, Folder 7)
    - Edwardes, Ethellone (Box 1616, Folder 8)
    - Ely, Edith Goodhue (Box 1616, Folder 9)
    - Goss, Stella Elizabeth (Box 1616, Folder 10)
    - Holden, Bertha Haynes (Box 1616, Folder 11)
    - McLellane, Myra (Box 1616, Folder 12)
    - McClure, Anna Margaret (Box 1616, Folder 13)
    - Montgomery, Beatrice (Box 1616, Folder 14)
    - Peirce, Marda (Box 1616, Folder 15)
    - Perkins, Louise Childs (Box 1616, Folder 16)
    - Rogers, Laura Mary (Box 1616, Folder 17)
    - Thalheimer, Ethel Seymour (Box 1616, Folder 18)
    - Westcott, Laura Johnson (Box 1616, Folder 19)
    - Wicker, Lucy Southwort (Box 1616, Folder 20)
    - Burbeck, Bertha May (Box 1616, Folder 21)
    - Butler, Mary Lucretia (Box 1616, Folder 22)
  - Individuals A-Bo (Box 1617)
  - Individuals Br-F (Box 1618)
  - Individuals G-H (Box 1618.1)
  - Individuals I-Om (Box 1619)
  - Individuals On-Pi (Box 1619.1)
  - Individuals Pl-Sh (Box 1620)
  - Individuals Sm-V (Box 1621)
  - Individuals W-Z (Box 1621.1)
  - Bancroft, Mary Louise (photo album) (Box 1621.2)
  - Bliss, Ethel May (memorabilia book) (Box 1622)
  - Burke, Adelaide Louise (scrapbook) (Box 1623.1)
  - French, Ruth Hawthorne (memorabilia book) (Box 1624)
  - Holman, Margaret (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1625)
  - Riggs, Martha Warner (correspondence, photographs) (Box 1626)
  - Sargent, Lydia Parrott (memorabilia book, reunion costume) (Box 1626.1)
  - Sawyer, Amy Wentworth (photo album) (Box 1621.2)
  - Tift, Henrietta Hawtin (photo albums) (Box 1621.2)
  - Tuttle, Berenice Rachel (memorabilia book) (Box 1629)
- Class of 1903 Records, 1899-1970; 11.396 linear feet (20 containers)
  The Class of 1903 was the twenty-fifth entering class and the twenty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1903 records, 1899-1970, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1903, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, minutes, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Frolic given by 1902, 1899 (Box 1630, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Grind by 1902, 1899 (Box 1630, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1899 (Box 1630, Folder 7)
  - Gifts, 1918; 1967 (Box 1630, Folder 8)
  - Granddaughters and Great-Granddaughter, 1965-1968 (Box 1630, Folder 9)
  - Groups-Photographs, 1899-1903 (Box 1630, Folder 10)
  - History, undated (Box 1630, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 13)
  - Jabberwock Block Print, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 14)
  - Junior Frolic, 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 15)
  - Junior Prom, 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 16)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 17)
  - Junior-Senior Party given by Class of 1904, 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 18)
  - Junior Ushers, 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 19)
  - Class Letters, 1939-1970 (Box 1630, Folder 20)
  - Minutes, 1899-1913 (Box 1631, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1899-1963 (Box 1631, Folder 2)
  - President's Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 1631, Folder 3)
  - Promenade Concert, 1903 (Box 1631, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1904 (Box 1631, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1906 (Box 1631, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1908 (Box 1631, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1913 (Box 1631, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1923 (Box 1631, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1928 (Box 1631, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1933 (Box 1631, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1938 (Box 1631, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1943 (Box 1631, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 1631, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1953 (Box 1631, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 1631, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 1631, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 1631, Folder 18)
  - Reunion Publications, 1913-1963 (Box 1631, Folder 19)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1631, Folder 20)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1903 (Box 1632, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1903 (Box 1632, Folder 2)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1632, Folder 3)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1901 (Box 1632, Folder 4)
  - Class Supper, 1903 (Box 1632, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1903-1922 (Box 1633, Folder 1)
  - Alumnae Days, 1923-1947 (Box 1633, Folder 2)
  - Alumnae Days, 1948-1964 (Box 1633, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records-General, 1903-1959 (Box 1634, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Obituaries A-W (Box 1634, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Records-A-Be (Box 1634, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Bl-Bu (Box 1634, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Records-C-Co (Box 1634, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Cr-Dr (Box 1634, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Du-E (Box 1634, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Records-F-Fr (Box 1634, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Fu-Gi (Box 1634, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Go-Gr (Box 1634, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Records-H-He (Box 1634, Folder 11)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Hi-Ho (Box 1634, Folder 12)
  - Class Secretary's Records-J-Ki (Box 1634, Folder 13)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Kn-Ma (Box 1634, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Records-N-Po (Box 1635, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Records-McC-McN (Box 1635, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Me-Mu (Box 1635, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Pu-Ru (Box 1635, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Records-S-Sh (Box 1635, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Records-St-Su (Box 1635, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Records-T-Wa (Box 1635, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Records-We-Z (Box 1635, Folder 8)
  - Reunion Memorabilia (Box 1635.1)
  - Individuals A-D (Box 1636)
  - Individuals E-Hi (Box 1637)
  - Individuals L-S (Box 1638)
  - Individuals St-Z (Box 1639)
  - Ames, Jessie (photo album) (Box 1640)
  - Ames, Jesse (scrapbook) (Box 1640.1)
  - Baker, Mary Ashby (photo album) (Box 1640.1)
  - Bogue, Anna Tefft (photo album) (Box 1640)
  - Booker, Myrta May (memorabilia book) (Box 1641)
  - Booker, Myrta May (scrapbook of travels in Germany) (Box 1641.1)
  - Keniston, Sarah Thorndike (scrapbook) (Box 1642.1)
  - Knight, Bessie Adele (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1642)
  - Lauriat, Blanche (photo album) (Box 1640)
  - McCutcheon, Margaret Wilson (photo album) (Box 1640)
  - McDowell, Clara (lecture and lab notes) (Box 1643)
  - Post, Laura (memorabilia book) (Box 1644)
  - Post, Laura (memorabilia book) (Box 1644.1)
- Class of 1904 Records, 1900-1979; 15.875 linear feet (36 containers)
  The Class of 1904 was the twenty-sixth entering class and the twenty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1904 records, 1900-1979, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1904, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, photo albums, letters, class secretary's notebook, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 1)
  - Bequests, 1968-1971 (Box 1645, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Frolic given by 1903, 1900 (Box 1645, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Grind by 1903, 1900 (Box 1645, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1900 (Box 1645, Folder 10)
  - Groups, 1900-1904 (Box 1645, Folder 11)
  - Groups- Photographs, 1900-1904 (Box 1645, Folder 12)
  - Class History, undated (Box 1645, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 14)
  - Ivy Day- Photographs, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 15)
  - Junior Prom, 1903 (Box 1645, Folder 16)
  - Junior-Senior Party, 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 17)
  - Junior Ushers, 1903 (Box 1645, Folder 18)
  - Junior Frolic, 1903 (Box 1645, Folder 19)
  - Smith Alumnae Quarterly, Class Notes, 1944-1977 (Box 1645, Folder 20)
  - Class Letters, 1944-1977 (Box 1645, Folder 21)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships, 1964-1974 (Box 1646, Folder 4)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1646, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1901 (Box 1646, Folder 6)
  - Class Supper, 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Notebook, 1907-1957 (Box 1647, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Notebook, 1954-1977 (Box 1647, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Notebook, 1905-1954 (Box 1647, Folder 3)
  - Photograph Album (Box 1648, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Album (Box 1648, Folder 2)
  - Photograph Album (Box 1648, Folder 3)
  - Reunions (Box 1649, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1905 (Box 1649, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1907 (Box 1649, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1909 (Box 1649, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1910 (Box 1649, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1919 (Box 1649, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1924 (Box 1649, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1925 (Box 1649, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1929 (Box 1649, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 1649, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1939 (Box 1649, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 1649, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1950-1952 (Box 1649, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 1649, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 1649, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1649, Folder 16)
  - Reunions- Photographs, 1964 (Box 1649, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 1649, Folder 18)
  - Reunion Album, 1959 (Box 1650, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Album, 1959 (Box 1650, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Album, 1959 (Box 1650, Folder 3)
  - Reunion Scrapbook- missing since 2/99
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 1652, Folder 1)
  - Reunions- Photographs, 1969 (Box 1652, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 1652, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 1652, Folder 4)
  - Reunion Scrapbook- missing since 2/99 (Box 1652.1)
  - Reunion Bags (Box 1652.1)
  - Class Secretary's card file (Box 1652.2)
  - Reunion memorabilia (Box 1652.2)
  - Reunion costume (Box 1652.3)
  - Miscellaneous (including stamps) (Box 1646.1)
  - Individuals A-Cil (Box 1653)
  - Individuals Cla-Gar (Box 1654)
  - Individuals Gay-H (Box 1655)
  - Individuals I-M (Box 1656)
  - Individuals N-Pho (Box 1657)
  - Individuals T-Z (Box 1658)
  - Buck, Grace Robertson (memorabilia book, photo albums) (Box 1659)
  - Burnham, Sophia Lord (memorabilia book) (Box 1659.1)
  - Chambers, Mary Ballard (memorabilia book) (Box 1659.2)
  - Comer, Mary (correspondence, photo album) (Box 1660)
  - Comer, Mary (memorabilia book lab notebook) (Box 1662.1)
  - Fuller, Luise Stetson (Box 1661)
  - Haynes, Muriel Sturgis (memorabilia book) (Box 1662)
  - Jones, Eleanor Poor (photo album) (Box 1661.1)
  - Kingsbury, Edith Wheeler (photo albums) (Box 1662.1)
  - Marble, Helen Chase (photo albums) (Box 1662.2)
  - McKelvey, Katherine Isabella (memorabilia book) (Box 1663)
  - Stein, Amy Esther (scrapbook) (Box 1663.1)
  - Telling, Elisabeth Irma (correspondence) (Box 1664)
  - Telling, Elisabeth Irma (correspondence) (Box 1665)
  - Trull, Evelyn (Class notes, photos, etc.) (Box 1666)
  - Trull, Evelyn (Correspondence) (Box 1667)
  - Trull, Evelyn (Correspondence) (Box 1668)
  - Trull, Evelyn (Correspondence) (Box 1669)
  - Trull, Evelyn (memorabilia book) (Box 1669.1)
- Class of 1905 Records, 1901-1975; 14.458 linear feet (17 containers)
  The Class of 1905 was the twenty-seventh entering class and the twenty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1905 records, 1901-1975, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1905, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, obituaries, financial information, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 3)
  - Descendants, 1934-1965 (Box 1670, Folder 4)
  - Donors to College Funds, undated (Box 1670, Folder 5)
  - Finances, 1954-1970 (Box 1670, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind by 1904, 1901 (Box 1670, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1901 (Box 1670, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1901-1905 (Box 1670, Folder 9)
  - Class History, undated (Box 1670, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom, 1904 (Box 1670, Folder 13)
  - Junior Ushers, 1904 (Box 1670, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1919-1975 (Box 1670, Folder 15)
  - Obituaries, Clippings, Letters, etc, 1905-1930 (Box 1684 A, Folder 1)
  - Weddings, Obituaries, Press Clippings, Class Letters, 1929-1957 (Box 1684 A, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Class Meetings, 1901-1950 (Box 1671, Folder 1)
  - Organization, undated (Box 1671, Folder 2)
  - Prayer Meetings, 1905 (Box 1671, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1671, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1908 (Box 1671, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1910 (Box 1671, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1915-1917 (Box 1671, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1920 (Box 1671, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1925 (Box 1671, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 1671, Folder 10)
  - Reunions- Book of Our Sons, 1932 (Box 1671, Folder 11)
  - Reunions- Book of Our Daughters, 1934 (Box 1671, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1935-1939 (Box 1671, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 1671, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1945 (Box 1671, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1950 (Box 1671, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 1672, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 1672, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 1672, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 1672, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 1672, Folder 5)
  - Reunion- Mad March Hare, 1927-1940 (Box 1672, Folder 6)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1672, Folder 7)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1672, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1902 (Box 1672, Folder 9)
  - Class Supper, 1905 (Box 1672, Folder 10)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 2)